Hello hello hello friends welcome to your
own YouTube channel BJP. Friends today
's video is going to be very special
because in 2021 we have released a new video
that in this way you can transfer your insurance sitting at home.
Friends if you have bought a second hand car
and you want to change its insurance sitting at home and do it in your
name here then
this video is absolutely right for you. You
always keep going around the agent
and ask him that in this way
you can transfer the insurance,
he shows you how to do it and
takes a lot of money from you. Now watch this video,
I have made a video of how
I am transferring the insurance of my car which is approved here.
I had the
back side etc. This is the
insurance of ICICI Lombard, I am showing you how to transfer it
and
in just Rs. 60 this matter gets transferred and the insurance is transferred,
I click on the given link, after that make the payment and write it down, the
company people have to deduct Rs. 60 from you there,
so let us continue
and after the link, your sister  Stripe is for its
payment
and what we will do here is enter the
mobile number associated with our Parsi, the
mobile number which we
want to join the party,
enter the email ID, after that we will register here,
what will happen after declaring, we will have to
visit the payment, Bhushan Batra will
get UP card, net banking etc., use
whichever method you like,
and what to do from there is make the
payment, as if you make the payment, then
here you will
get a test like this that you have made the
payment, you will send ₹100 here,
I have done this through UPA's metro, so this money of mine has gone to UPA
's battery saver mode, send message, then
Rs. 60 is approved, we
can transfer this express online, so here it will tell us
that we can make the payment and
after commenting, we get the response within three to four
days,
a state-of-the-art element has been taken up and has
reached our system and
We will take a screenshot of this
and keep it and we will get the policy in a few days
but friends the big thing is
how will you
get this link, you will get this link, you just have to make the payment,
after making the payment your
insurance gets transferred within a day,
let's talk about it, we will
get this link application, friends first of all what
you have to do is this is only
for those people who
want to transfer insurance from ICC,
so here I am giving you a number, take a
note of this number and
call on it, the customer care will talk to you, your
policy number will be asked, the opposite party is
yours which is in the name of someone else and in the
future they can ask you for its vehicle
number, they can ask for
your insurance number,
you have to give the details of the policy, after that
you have to give it to your detective this evening,
after that they
will generate a click for your email for your number, then
you will get a link, after that you have to make the
payment, you just have to call on this number,
you don't have to do anything,
I am giving it to you within the company, you
just have to go to this  What are you doing? You have to call
and after that you have to tell that we have to
transfer our term insurance,
after that you will click on the link and make the
payment, your insurance will be transferred inside Din Dhan, a very
simple method friends, I hope you
liked the video, if you liked it then definitely like it.